

# **GRIFFIN BOYD**



griffinaugustboyd@gmail.com



541-261-7329



2304 Enfield Rd. Austin, Texas 78703

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Adobe Illustrator 000000000 Adobe InDesign 00000000 Adobe Photoshop 000000000 Microsoft Word 000000000 Microsoft Excel 000000000

### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Communication Organization Work Ethic Team Player 000000000 000000000 Coachable





## **PROFILE**

A self-monivated individual, who is driven to learn each and every day. Bringing to you a background in both sales, and customer service. Using what I have learned from being a student-athlete, as well as my work experience, to help improve your buisness.



## **EDUCATION**

# Western Oregon University 2010-2013

Student Athlete

Bachelor of Science Degree in Communication Studies

Major: BA Communications Minor: BA Sports Management Graduation date: June 2013



# JOB EXPERIENCE

# INTERNATIONAL SPORTS MANAGEMENT 07/2013-10/2013

Account Executive

- -Builds business by identifying & selling prospects
- -Research leads & Identifies potential prospects for International Sporting Events
- -Cold calling & selling packages by establishing relationships with prospects
- -Communicate with Fortune 500 Executives
- -Maintains quality service by establishing & enforcing organization standards
- -Contributes to team effort by accomplishing results

### MEDFORD ROGUES BASEBALL 11/2013 - 09/2014

Assistant General Manager

- -Hire Summer Interns
- -Schedule Events to be held at the field during the summer
- -Acquire and Manage sponsorship Accounts
- -Sell advertisement space at facility
- -Order merchandise for fan purchase
- -Scout players during the year to play on team
- -Marketing and PR for the organization

## **GURU INK 09/2014 - 03/2015**

Account Manager

- -Develop Leads
- -Sell Service
- -Customer Relations
- -Product Specialists

### UNCLE BILLY'S BREWERY 04/2014- 09/2015

- -Finalize dish presentation
- -Run food

Server

- -Share my knowlege of both food and drink menus.
- -Accurately record and submit orders into system.
- -Assist any customer with questions on our menu or about our brewery.